bannerbuzz.com 2019-04-18

# BannerBuzz.com: Privacy Policy

Your data is important to us

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices of bannerbuzz.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It covers the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how is it used and with whom it maybe shared.
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  * How can you correct any inaccuracies in the information.

##### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing:

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will continue to provide the highest quality and lowest prices, to generate the highest customer satisfaction, and to be the supplier of choice for the online banner and sign market.

We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, except when needed to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or notify you of changes to this privacy policy.

##### Your access to and control over information:

You may opt out of any future contact from us at any time. By contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website, you can do any of these:

  * Check the data you have shared with us.
  * Change, correct of delete that data.
  * Ask questions about how we are using your data.

##### Security:

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via our website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us securely. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for 'https' at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) can access personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are in a safe, secure environment.

##### Registration:

In order to use our website, a user, must fill out a registration form or provide details at checkout. During registration, you will be asked for certain information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the products/services on our site that you have expressed an interest in.

##### Orders:

To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). We only use this information for billing and fulfilling your order. For instance, if we have trouble processing your order, we’ll use this information to contact you.

##### Cookies:

We use 'cookies' on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to identify repeat visitors and help us improve your access to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you don't have to log in with a password more than once, hence saving your time. Cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users and enhance their experience on our site. Using ookies is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

##### Links:

The website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those other sites. We encourage you to be careful when you leave our site and thoroughly read, and read the privacy statements of all other sites that collect personally identifiable information.

##### Your consent:

You acknowledge that this privacy policy is part of the terms of service and you agree that using this site signifies your consent to and agreement with Bannerbuzz’s privacy policy. Bannerbuzz reserves the right to change the terms of service, including this privacy policy, at any time, without advance notice. If Bannerbuzz decides to change this privacy policy, it will post those changes on this page, so that you are aware of what information is collected, how is it used and under what circumstances is it disclosed.

* * *

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy,  
Contact us immediately via phone 1-800-580-4489 or via email to sales@bannerbuzz.com.
